<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Uncategorized Archives - Gran Malecón del Río</title>
	<atom:link href="/blog/category/uncategorized/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/blog/category/uncategorized/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 20:07:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>es</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://fastandstatic-offload-granmalecon.s3.amazonaws.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/11140157/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Uncategorized Archives - Gran Malecón del Río</title>
	<link>/blog/category/uncategorized/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Gran Malecón&#8217;s self-care culture during the last season of the year</title>
		<link>/blog/the-gran-malecons-self-care-culture-during-the-last-season-of-the-year/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[eme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 20:07:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://granmalecon.com/?p=1615</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Since Christmas lights were turn on, on December first through a live transmission, Barranquilla´s mayoralty invited people to stay in family and be safe during this season of the year. The Gran Malecón, as one of the locations with Christmas illumination in Barranquilla, was outstanding for its visitor’s behavior and it positive results with the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/blog/the-gran-malecons-self-care-culture-during-the-last-season-of-the-year/">The Gran Malecón&#8217;s self-care culture during the last season of the year</a> appeared first on <a href="/">Gran Malecón del Río</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Since Christmas lights were turn on, on December first through a live transmission, Barranquilla´s mayoralty invited people to stay in family and be safe during this season of the year.</p>



<p>The Gran Malecón, as one of the locations with Christmas illumination in Barranquilla, was outstanding for its visitor’s behavior and it positive results with the biosecurity measures. During December 2020 we received around 500 thousand visitors, that represents 23% of the visitors from 2019, as a result of a hard job on capacity control, physical distancing and compliance with all Biosafety protocols.</p>



<p>With the support of Transit Secretariat, Urban control and public space Secretariat, Security and City convivence office, District Police and COVID patrol, the Gran Malecon´s operations team has made an efficient manage facing visitor’s circulation mostly during the time frame of 6:00 PM to 8:00 PM on weekends.</p>



<p>“Smile with your eyes” and “Take your distance and take care of your family” were some of the messages that visitors received during their visit, as well as signaling, guides and social media to provide information constantly about Gran Malecon limit capacity and good behavior manners</p>



<p>Coordination and logistics have generated a positive overview and safe experience in each space of the Gran Malecón, however, visitors have taken an important role to continue having Barranquilla´s population enjoying our locations by the river. Since the reopening on August 20, we have received 1,539,168 visits specially for activities as individual exercise, skaters, cycling as well as commerce consumption, helping the economic reactivation. On December the Caiman del Río had 1,400,000 million on sales.</p>



<p>The invitation for Barranquilla´s people and tourists is to continue having a proper behavior on every public location as the Gran Malecón, where they can enjoy nature and the environment.</p>
<p>The post <a href="/blog/the-gran-malecons-self-care-culture-during-the-last-season-of-the-year/">The Gran Malecón&#8217;s self-care culture during the last season of the year</a> appeared first on <a href="/">Gran Malecón del Río</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Videos and photos</title>
		<link>/blog/videos-and-photos/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[eme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 19:45:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://granmalecon.com/?p=1288</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Every recording, production and photo study that take place at the Gran Malecon requires a previous permission and request. The permission is required for photography and videos in every open space, Puerta de Oro sector, Gastronomic sector (not Caiman del Río), the sport&#160; recreative sector, 72nd street and 78th street entrance. (Permission on areas as [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/blog/videos-and-photos/">Videos and photos</a> appeared first on <a href="/">Gran Malecón del Río</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Every recording, production and photo study that take place at the Gran Malecon requires a previous permission and request.</p>



<p>The permission is required for photography and videos in every open space, Puerta de Oro sector, Gastronomic sector (not Caiman del Río), the sport&nbsp; recreative sector, 72nd street and 78th street entrance. (Permission on areas as public Street and river avenue should be requested directly to Barranquilla´s mayoralty)</p>



<p>According to Decree 0732 of 2020 of the Mayor of Barranquilla, the mask is OBLIGATORY for EVERYONE. Specially on the public transportation system and in areas where there is a massive fluence of people (Market plazas, supermarkets, banks, pharmacies) as well as open public spaces.</p>



<p>To take photography and videos is necessary to fill out a letter of commitment. Through this commitment letter we want to give priority on privacy rights and user security. Each photo and video in the Gran Malecón for publication and divulgation purposes must follow the space values ​​and integrity in compliance with the code of conduct of the National Tourism Registry. RNT. 46722.Permissions required</p>



<p>Audiovisual and photography production projects should be requested previously to email <a href="mailto:info@puertadeoro.org">info@puertadeoro.org</a> taking in account the following requirments:</p>



<p>Recording or photo studio for editorial or commercial purposes</p>



<ul class="wp-block-list"><li>Activity duration</li><li>Number of team members</li><li>Quantity of production equipment</li><li>Space required</li></ul>



<p>*Photo studies for marriage or fifteen years celebration also require prior permission.</p>



<p>REGULATIONS:</p>



<ul class="wp-block-list"><li>Schedule and possible assemblies must be previously approved by the administration.</li><li>Logistics and assembly personnel must present their RLA.</li><li>If necessary, comply with the necessary permits generated by the activity to be developed.</li><li>The space requested must stay in perfect condition and free of waste.</li><li>It is strictly forbidden to intervene in the floor, use trees and planters.</li><li>Refreshments and gastronomic services are conditioned as exclusivity for commercial points of the Gran Malecon and the Cayman del Rio gastronomic market. It is not allowed to have snacks, hydration by third parties.</li><li>For the Cayman del Rio a separate application is required to caimandelrio@puertadeoro.org under approval and possible value for use of space.</li></ul>



<p>PERMISSION REQUEST</p>



<ul class="wp-block-list"><li>Email to <a href="mailto:info@puertadeoro.org">info@puertadeoro.org</a> describing activity with contact number, date, space, time, type of content and required equipment.</li><li>According to your request you will receive a response or you will be contacted in the next 7 days.</li></ul>
<p>The post <a href="/blog/videos-and-photos/">Videos and photos</a> appeared first on <a href="/">Gran Malecón del Río</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Caimán del Rio Reopening</title>
		<link>/blog/caiman-del-rio-reopening/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[eme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 19:40:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://granmalecon.com/?p=1281</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Caimán del Rio is reinvented to receive Barranquilla’s people again, following the biosecurity measures protocols together with 21 different kitchens that were expecting to turn on their stoves again. From 25 kitchens that make part of the gastronomic market, 21 are participating in Barranquilla&#8217;s reactivation since Thursday, August 2020. On visitor&#8217;s arrival, the new [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/blog/caiman-del-rio-reopening/">Caimán del Rio Reopening</a> appeared first on <a href="/">Gran Malecón del Río</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p> </p>



<p>The Caimán del Rio is reinvented to receive Barranquilla’s people again, following the biosecurity measures protocols together with 21 different kitchens that were expecting to turn on their stoves again. From 25 kitchens that make part of the gastronomic market, 21 are participating in Barranquilla&#8217;s reactivation since Thursday, August 2020.</p>



<p>On visitor&#8217;s arrival, the new protocols are: temperature measurement, hand disinfection, booking confirmation, menu with QR code, the consumption will take place only in the terrace with limited capacity. Once costumers leave the place, Caiman´s del Rio staff is in charge of the table disinfection.</p>



<p>This is a magic place with different stories behind its name. We have defined this place inspired in the alligator’s alimentation which is the most essential moment for this specie. Those moments are: Better in the evening, always at the rivers shore and sweet wait. Each kitchen represents one of these moments.</p>



<p>Caimán del Río is one of the 30 gastronomic business that made part of the commercial reactivation strategies, this strategy was created by Barranquilla´s mayoralty.</p>



<p>How to book? Go to www.granmalecon.com fill out the form correctly and show the email confirmation at Caiman´s del Rio entrance.</p>



<p>How purchase one of the merchandising collection? Remember that your purchase is a contribution to the maintenance of the Gran Malecón. For more information contact us through</p>



<p>WhatsApp (313) 391 47 83.</p>
<p>The post <a href="/blog/caiman-del-rio-reopening/">Caimán del Rio Reopening</a> appeared first on <a href="/">Gran Malecón del Río</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Biosecurity measurements for individual exercise</title>
		<link>/blog/biosecurity-measurements-for-individual-exercise/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[eme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 14:20:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://granmalecon.com/?p=1142</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Following the new measures announced by Barranquilla´s major Jaime Pumarejo on august 8th, the Gran Malecon has reopen only for individual exercise, after 4 months being closed. People between 19 and 69 years old may come in, on two different schedules: From 5:00 am to 8:00 am. and from 5:00 p.m. to 8: 00 p.m. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/blog/biosecurity-measurements-for-individual-exercise/">Biosecurity measurements for individual exercise</a> appeared first on <a href="/">Gran Malecón del Río</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Following the new measures announced by Barranquilla´s major Jaime Pumarejo on august 8th, the Gran Malecon has reopen only for individual exercise, after 4 months being closed.</strong></p>



<p><strong>People between 19 and 69 years old may come in, on two different schedules: From 5:00 am to 8:00 am. and from 5:00 p.m. to 8: 00 p.m. ID number won’t be required.</strong></p>



<p><strong>Seniors above 70 years old may come in daily as well for individual exercise from 4:00 p.m. to 6:00 p.m.&nbsp; For children between 2 to 17 years old are allowed to come in with only one parent or guardian on Tuesdays, Thursdays and Sundays, from 3:00 p.m. to 5:00 p.m.</strong></p>



<p><strong>Our team of guides at the Gran Malecon supported by Secretariat of Traffic and Mobility, Covid Patrol and Metropolitan Police, has stablished 3 access located on PDO Sector, 78th street and 72th street. On each control access they would take care of:</strong></p>



<p>·&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; <strong>Gran Malecón capacity control</strong></p>



<p>·&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; <strong>People temperature </strong></p>



<p>·&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; <strong>Use of mask</strong></p>



<p>·&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; <strong>Social Distance</strong></p>



<p>·         <strong>Gran Malecon Schedule for individual exercise</strong></p>



<p><strong>*The Gran Malecón would have only its 30% capacity.</strong></p>
<p>The post <a href="/blog/biosecurity-measurements-for-individual-exercise/">Biosecurity measurements for individual exercise</a> appeared first on <a href="/">Gran Malecón del Río</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Merchandising Caimán del Río</title>
		<link>/blog/merchandising-caiman-del-rio-2/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[eme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 14:17:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://granmalecon.com/?p=1140</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Now you can take Caiman´s del Rio characters anywhere! Whit this collection we want all our visitors to have a souvenir about Caiman del Rio, remembering all these magic characters reflected on T-shirts, agendas, mugs and hats.&#160; These articles make part of the first collection #Camianbutterflyeffect. Remember that your purchase is a contribution to the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/blog/merchandising-caiman-del-rio-2/">Merchandising Caimán del Río</a> appeared first on <a href="/">Gran Malecón del Río</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Now you can take Caiman´s del Rio characters anywhere! Whit this collection we want all our visitors to have a souvenir about Caiman del Rio, remembering all these magic characters reflected on T-shirts, agendas, mugs and hats.&nbsp; These articles make part of the first collection #Camianbutterflyeffect.</strong></p>



<p><strong>Remember that your purchase is a contribution to the maintenance of the Gran Malecón. For more information contact us through WhatsApp (313) 391 47 83.</strong></p>
<p>The post <a href="/blog/merchandising-caiman-del-rio-2/">Merchandising Caimán del Río</a> appeared first on <a href="/">Gran Malecón del Río</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Biosecurity Protocol</title>
		<link>/blog/merchandising-caiman-del-rio/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[eme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 14:13:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://granmalecon.com/?p=1134</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Safety and health at job are an important subject for all workers to complete their activities. This social historic moment that we are through because of the pandemic COVID-19, makes us to stablish measures to protect health and the life of our workers community. Biosecurity protocol is a guarantee of security and protection for either [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/blog/merchandising-caiman-del-rio/">Biosecurity Protocol</a> appeared first on <a href="/">Gran Malecón del Río</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<pre class="wp-block-preformatted"></pre>



<p><strong>Safety and health at job are an
important subject for all workers to complete their activities. This social
historic moment that we are through because of the pandemic COVID-19, makes us
to stablish measures to protect health and the life of our workers community.
Biosecurity protocol is a guarantee of security and protection for either
workers and visitor in a same space, keeping a healthy environment.</strong></p>



<p><strong>The protocol preventive
measurements are:</strong></p>



<ol class="wp-block-list"><li><strong>Obligatory use of mask</strong></li><li><strong>Social distance, at least 2 meters between two persons.</strong></li><li><strong>Constantly hand wash</strong></li><li><strong>Enforcement on cleaning and disinfection </strong></li><li><strong>Waste management</strong></li><li><strong>Proper use of PPI </strong></li></ol>



<p></p>
<p>The post <a href="/blog/merchandising-caiman-del-rio/">Biosecurity Protocol</a> appeared first on <a href="/">Gran Malecón del Río</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>CAIMAN 2 GO</title>
		<link>/blog/caiman-2-go/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[eme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 21:34:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://granmalecon.com/?p=1131</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>It starts between the juncture of the pandemic COVID-19, as an act of resilience and connection with our community supporting the Gran Malecon’s principles, with All the gastronomic offer, including the Caiman del Rio. A native specie on the river environment: The alligator (El Caimán). The inspiration of Caiman del Rio´s gastronomic market, now is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/blog/caiman-2-go/">CAIMAN 2 GO</a> appeared first on <a href="/">Gran Malecón del Río</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>It starts between the juncture of
the pandemic COVID-19, as an act of resilience and connection with our
community supporting the Gran Malecon’s principles, with All the gastronomic
offer, including the Caiman del Rio.</strong></p>



<p><strong>A native specie on the river
environment: The alligator (El Caimán). The inspiration of Caiman del Rio´s
gastronomic market, now is having a new objective to travel in order to take
all the gastronomic experiences on the Gran Malecon and Caiman del Rio to
Barranquilla´s homes.</strong></p>



<p><strong>From the river with love your
favorite recipes are being cooked. Follow our social network @caimandelrio</strong></p>
<p>The post <a href="/blog/caiman-2-go/">CAIMAN 2 GO</a> appeared first on <a href="/">Gran Malecón del Río</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Clams Fishers History</title>
		<link>/blog/clams-fishers-history/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[eme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 19:26:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://granmalecon.com/?p=879</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>[vc_row][vc_column][vc_column_text]“It began as a need. When I arrived to Palermo there was nothing to do. I asked to my father in law how to earn money and he told me, by getting out clams from river. Without knowing the whole procedure, I told him that there was any problem since I knew how to deal [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/blog/clams-fishers-history/">Clams Fishers History</a> appeared first on <a href="/">Gran Malecón del Río</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>[vc_row][vc_column][vc_column_text]“It began as a need. When I arrived to Palermo there was nothing to do. I asked to my father in law how to earn money and he told me, by getting out clams from river. Without knowing the whole procedure, I told him that there was any problem since I knew how to deal with waters situations. The first time I did it (for 3 days), I felt as not coming back. It was a disaster” However he came back, although they didn’t know how to get profits from this activity at the beginning, through th e years it became a support for 20 families in Palermo. “We all moved there and I even became an entrepreneur thanks to the Clam”</p>
<p>“For many years we were clam&#8217;s fishers, but now we have decided to become ecotourism pioneers on the Magdalena river.” This idea came out as a result for looking life quality for families that intend to show through tours, nature diversity that can be appreciated in this region and clams fishing activity history that long time ago makes part of their life. A talent they were born with and remains tattooed on their skin.</p>
<p>The river is in on their veins.</p>
<p>Now, they are an amphibian culture that protect and live for its conservation. They have changed a harmful activity, knowing the importance of protecting nature resources.</p>
<p>Their offer is based on three principle tours, that were designed in team work with Colombian Nationals Nature parks and families benefited from this project: Island 72 tour, The clam tour and Pensilvanian&#8217;s Island tour.[/vc_column_text][/vc_column][/vc_row][vc_row][vc_column][boc_img_gallery fixed_size=»yes» image_ids=»561,562,563,564&#8243;][/vc_column][/vc_row]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/blog/clams-fishers-history/">Clams Fishers History</a> appeared first on <a href="/">Gran Malecón del Río</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Opening of the recreational sector of the Gran Malecon</title>
		<link>/blog/opening-of-the-recreational-sector-of-the-gran-malecon/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[eme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2019 19:24:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://granmalecon.com/?p=873</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>[vc_row][vc_column][vc_column_text]El 23 de noviembre de 2019, el Gran Malecón creó para las familias nuevos espacios de diversión, esparcimiento y sana convivencia. Son 1,5 kilómetros divididos en 14 fabulosos espacios entre parques funcionales, zonas verdes y canchas deportivas que cambiarán por completo la dinámica recreativa de la ciudad junto al Río Grandes y chicos podrán disfrutar [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/blog/opening-of-the-recreational-sector-of-the-gran-malecon/">Opening of the recreational sector of the Gran Malecon</a> appeared first on <a href="/">Gran Malecón del Río</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>[vc_row][vc_column][vc_column_text]El 23 de noviembre de 2019, el Gran Malecón creó para las familias nuevos espacios de diversión, esparcimiento y sana convivencia. Son 1,5 kilómetros divididos en 14 fabulosos espacios entre parques funcionales, zonas verdes y canchas deportivas que cambiarán por completo la dinámica recreativa de la ciudad junto al Río Grandes y chicos podrán disfrutar con el Parque del Agua, Jardín Nativo, la Plaza de los Marinos, parques para la primera infancia y para niños grandes, canchas múltiples, zonas verdes, arborización y todo lo que representa el contacto con la naturaleza por tener en frente el río que nos vio nacer.[/vc_column_text][/vc_column][/vc_row][vc_row][vc_column][boc_img_gallery image_ids=»590,591,592&#8243;][/vc_column][/vc_row]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/blog/opening-of-the-recreational-sector-of-the-gran-malecon/">Opening of the recreational sector of the Gran Malecon</a> appeared first on <a href="/">Gran Malecón del Río</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Opening of the first gastronomic market in Barranquilla «Caiman del Rio»</title>
		<link>/blog/opening-of-the-first-gastronomic-market-in-barranquilla-caiman-del-rio/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[eme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2019 19:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://granmalecon.com/?p=867</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>[vc_row][vc_column][vc_column_text]On October 23 of 2019, Barranquilla was witness on how the Caiman arrived and stayed at Magdalena shore. Local food, as rice, fried food, roast food, Arabic food, sea feed, poke and different healthy options, as well as dessert and liquor were put together under the same ceiling paying tribute to international cuisine and highlight [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/blog/opening-of-the-first-gastronomic-market-in-barranquilla-caiman-del-rio/">Opening of the first gastronomic market in Barranquilla «Caiman del Rio»</a> appeared first on <a href="/">Gran Malecón del Río</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>[vc_row][vc_column][vc_column_text]On October 23 of 2019, Barranquilla was witness on how the Caiman arrived and stayed at Magdalena shore. Local food, as rice, fried food, roast food, Arabic food, sea feed, poke and different healthy options, as well as dessert and liquor were put together under the same ceiling paying tribute to international cuisine and highlight the native flavors of the city in 25 different kitchens in a 2,200 m2 space.</p>
<p>Visiting Caiman del Rio experience brings with it 3 categories inspired by the alligator&#8217;s instincts as a specie to have the ideal prey. “Better in the evening”, when the alligator waits for the best moment to get his prey at the end of the day, represents the possibility to enjoy the night in a space with pairings. “Always in the river shore”, a zone where most of species that the alligator eats are located, in the market means high quality and a variety offer of main food. “With sweet wait” is an alligator habit to recognize that tastiest meal comes at the right moment, which means enjoying pause with the best coffee and dessert at the end of the day.</p>
<p>The manager of the gastronomic market Alvaro Boom Malkun, said that the Caiman del Rio intention was to lump together on the same building “The fact, that in Barranquilla you can find the best Chinese food, Italian food, the best hotdog, among other typical food” as a “re born of immigrant cuisine”.[/vc_column_text][/vc_column][/vc_row]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/blog/opening-of-the-first-gastronomic-market-in-barranquilla-caiman-del-rio/">Opening of the first gastronomic market in Barranquilla «Caiman del Rio»</a> appeared first on <a href="/">Gran Malecón del Río</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
